ERICA MARANOWSKI

SUMMARY

I'm experienced with JavaScript and Python, coming from a background in SPSS for data.

My early career in data evaluation led me to software development.

As coding grew into a larger part of my work, it became a natural fit and my eventual focus.

PROJECTS

BanKan | live | repo

• organization + productivity

VancouberEats | live | repo

e-commerce

MeetBuds | live | repo

• activities + networking

GET IN TOUCH



971.340.6684



emaranowski@gmail.com



emaranowski.com



LinkedIn



GitHub



Wellfound

EDUCATION

App Academy | Full Stack Development | 2023

Python · Flask · JavaScript · Express.js · Sequelize.js · React.js Redux.js · Node.js · PostgreSQL · SQLite · HTML5 · CSS3

Reed College | BA: Sociology | 2015

- Analyzed data using R and Stata.
- Awarded full financial aid.

EXPERIENCE

Evaluation Specialist

Neighborhood Partnerships | Nov 2019 – Mar 2023

Coded in SPSS to clean and analyze program data. Managed and updated program database. Organized findings via charts and tables. Ensured equitable and rigorous research design. Updated website using HTML/CSS.

Linguistic Tester

Welocalize | Apr 2020 - Apr 2021

Analyzed linguistic data using stringent quality standards. Employed knowledge of localized language traits. Identified, categorized, and documented issues via tracking database.

Resource Specialist

The Cupcake Girls | Apr 2017 - Nov 2019

Optimized and structured resource databases. Researched partners to provide appropriate client support. Screened for equity in partners' practices and our own.

Research Analyst & Project Manager

Interaction Metrics | Jun 2015 - Dec 2016

Designed surveys and interviews (structured and open-ended). Sampled, operationalized, and cleaned data. Qual. and quant. analysis to identify B2B and B2C issues. Presented findings with quotes, tables, charts, and statistics using Excel, Word, and PowerPoint. Wrote articles on research methodology. Updated website using HTML/CSS.